Lose your innocence... or lose your life.
Cherry Falls is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Geoffrey Wright.
When students in the small town of Cherry Falls learn a serial killer is targeting virgins,
they realize their only chance of survival is to throw a “Pop Your Cherry” party.
Jody Marken, played by Brittany Murphy.
Leonard Marliston, played by Jay Mohr.
Sherrif Brent Marken, played by Michael Biehn.
Rod Harper, played by Jesse Bradford.
Marge Marken, played by Candy Clark.
Kenny Ascott, played by Gabriel Mann.
Cherry Falls is a 1999 American slasher film directed by Geoffrey Wright,
and starring Brittany Murphy, Jay Mohr, and Michael Biehn.
The plot focuses on a small Virginia town where a serial
killer is targeting teenaged virgins.
After being submitted to and rejected by the MPAA numerous times, Cherry Falls premiered in May 1999 at Marché du Film in France and subsequently
screened at several film festivals in some countries in early 2000, but did not have a theatrical release in the United States.
Finally it was purchased by USA Films, who telecast it in the fall of 2000.
The film explores themes of virgin, high school, small town, rape, psychopath.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.